Guide to the Harrison Lee papers, 1928-1992 MS2011
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Community and business organizations, 1988-1992; MS2011 Series 2; 2 Linear feet
  - Chinatown Steering Committee: Minutes, attendance list, proposal for 730 5th St project, 1990 February 08 (Box 5, Folder 71)
  - Chinatown Steering Committee: Zoning Commission hearing, 1990 March 02 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Chinatown Steering Committee: Minutes, attendance list, agenda, 1990 March 12 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Chinatown Steering Committee: Minutes, agenda, 1990 April 02 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Chinatown Steering Committee: Agenda, 1990 April 14 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Chinatown Steering Committee: Correspondence -- rejection of proposed offer for community space by the Far East Center, 1990 May 18 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Chinatown Steering Committee: Meeting notice, attached copy of 1988 By-Laws, agenda, 1990 June 04 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Chinatown Steering Committee: July 9 1990 -- Meeting notice, agenda, 1990 July 09 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Chinatown Steering Committee: Correspondence "Chinatown Design review Procedure", 1990 July 14 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Chinatown Steering Committee: Correspondence -- The Building/Square 429, 1990 November 02 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Chinatown Steering Committee: Agenda, 1990 November 05 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Chinatown Steering Committee: Minutes, 1991 February 04 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Chinatown Steering Committee: Agenda, 1991 March 04 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Chinatown Steering Committee: Minutes, agenda, 1992 June 03 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Chinatown Steering Committee: Agenda, minutes, 1991 July 01 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Chinatown Steering Committee: Agenda, minutes, plans concerning 740 6th St, 1991 August 05 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Chinatown Steering Committee: Agenda, 1991 September 09 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Chinatown Steering Committee: Meeting notice, agenda, minutes, lantern designs, 1991 December 02 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Chinatown Steering Committee: Agenda, minutes, dues statements, 1992 February 03 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Chinatown Steering Committee: March 2 1992 -- Agenda, minutes, The Shakespeare Theatre presentation, 1992 March 02 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Chinatown Steering Committee: Agenda, 1992 October 05 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Chinatown Steering Committee: Agenda, status report of 810 7th St., 1992 September 14 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Chinatown Steering Committee: Sign Design Sketch, 1992 November 09 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Chinatown Steering Committee: Correspondence -- proposed amendments to the District Elements of the Comprehensive plan, 1992 December 31 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Chinatown Steering Committee: Correspondence -- request of Chinese Arch, 1992 December 31 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Chinatown Steering Committee: Meeting notice, agenda, Chinatown program: review of 1992, 1993 January 04 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Chinatown Steering Committee: Miscellaneous -- List of Associates in Chinatown, undated (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Chinese Consolidated Benevolent Association of Washington, DC: By-laws and regulations in pamphlet form, undated (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Chinese Consolidated Benevolent Association of Washington, DC: Correspondence -- addition of Chinese motifs to Gallery Place Metro Station, 1975 April 18 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Chinese Consolidated Benevolent Association of Washington, DC: Correspondence -- Don't Tear it Down Citizen's Action Group, 1976 June 10 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Chinese Consolidated Benevolent Association of Washington, DC: Correspondence -- WRC-TV editorial, 1976 June 21 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Chinese Consolidated Benevolent Association of Washington, DC: Documents and follow-up correspondence dealing with the American Bicentennial grand parade, 1976 July 03 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Chinese Consolidated Benevolent Association of Washington, DC: Correspondence -- Letter of resignation from CCBA's secretarial position, 1976 July 09 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Chinese Consolidated Benevolent Association of Washington, DC: Association's involvement in the Street for People Dedication Committee, 1977 March 29 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Chinese Consolidated Benevolent Association of Washington, DC: Association's involvement in the development of the Wah Luck House, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Chinese Consolidated Benevolent Association of Washington, DC: Financial and Accounting Final report, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Chinese Consolidated Benevolent Association of Washington, DC: Tax Exempt Status and Original Statement of Election, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Chinese Consolidated Benevolent Association of Washington, DC: Various Drafts of By-Laws, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Chinese Consolidated Benevolent Association of Washington, DC: Translation of By-Laws into Cantonese, 1982 March 10 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Chinese Consolidated Benevolent Association of Washington, DC: Final Revised Statement of Election and By-laws, 1983 May 26 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Chinese Consolidated Benevolent Association of Washington, DC: Association membership list, 1987 April 13 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Chinese Consolidated Benevolent Association of Washington, DC: Chinese American Community Leaders meet with the Deputy Mayor, 1987 April 23 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Chinese Consolidated Benevolent Association of Washington, DC: Meeting Notices, 1983-1989 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Chinese Consolidated Benevolent Association of Washington, DC: Application for Tax Exemption, 1984 October (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Chinese Consolidated Benevolent Association of Washington, DC: Proposed Property Exchange of 803 H street, 1992 February 25 (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Chinese Consolidated Benevolent Association of Washington, DC: Various forms and receipts, undated (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - Washington Chinatown Development Company Incorporation: Sketches for Seal, 1977 November 18 (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - Washington Chinatown Development Company Incorporation: Articles of Incorporation and later amendments, 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - Washington Chinatown Development Company Incorporation: Organization's By-Laws, various drafts in both English and Chinese, 1980-1982 (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - Washington Chinatown Development Company Incorporation: Minutes, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - Washington Chinatown Development Company Incorporation: Minutes, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - Washington Chinatown Development Company Incorporation: Minutes, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - Washington Chinatown Development Company Incorporation: Minutes, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Washington Chinatown Development Company Incorporation: Minutes, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Washington Chinatown Development Company Incorporation: Minutes, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Washington Chinatown Development Company Incorporation: Minutes, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Washington Chinatown Development Company Incorporation: Director Certification papers, 1983 July 24 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Washington Chinatown Development Company Incorporation: Minutes, combined meeting of board of directors and advisors, 1992 January (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Washington Chinatown Development Company Incorporation: Documents detailing Limited Partnership Agreement and relating to construction of Wah Luck house, 1979-1982 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Washington Chinatown Development Company Incorporation: Organizational Tax Exemption, Correspondence and Application, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Washington Chinatown Development Company Incorporation: Financial statements, 1980-1983 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Washington Chinatown Development Company Incorporation: Promotional materials, "The Arch: Buy a Ticket for our Future" flyers, tickets, guest list, 1979 December (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Washington Chinatown Development Company Incorporation: Sketch for Corporate seal, 1977 November (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Chinatown Economic Development Corporation: Articles of Incorporation, 1982 June 30 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Chinatown Economic Development Corporation: Organization's By-Laws, undated (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Chinatown Economic Development Corporation: Minutes, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Chinatown Economic Development Corporation: Correspondence, Gallery Place North project, 1982 November 04 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Downtown Partnership: DC Downtown Partnership - defined, undated (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Downtown Partnership: Community Outreach Meeting -- Purpose Statement and List of standing Teams, after September 1984, undated (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Downtown Partnership: Membership Rosters, undated (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Downtown Partnership: Original "Standing Teams" and Restatement of Objectives, undated (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Downtown Partnership: Co-Chairman's Security Initiatives, 1986 July 17 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Downtown Partnership: Agenda, team progress report, 1986 July 24 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Downtown Partnership: Agenda, work plan for 1987, minutes, 1986 October 30 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Downtown Partnership: Agenda, minutes, 1987 January 15 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Downtown Partnership: Executive Summary of retail Action Committee Meeting, 1987 March 14 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Downtown Partnership: Team progress report, 1987 April 22 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Downtown Partnership: Management Entity, 1987 May 12 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Downtown Partnership: July 22 1987 -- Agenda, preservation of small buildings, minutes, 1987 July 22 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Downtown Partnership: Articles of Incorporation, October July, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Downtown Partnership: Strategic Planning Session, 1987 October 14 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Downtown Partnership: Team Briefing: Background History, undated (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Downtown Partnership: List of Members, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Downtown Partnership: Agenda, minutes, 1988 March 23 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Downtown Partnership: Organization's By-Laws, report on Preserving Small Buildings Downtown, Process for Establishing A Special Improvement District, 1988 February 09 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Downtown Partnership: Agenda, nominations for board of directors, 1987 Annual Report, 1988 May 11 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Downtown Partnership: Agenda, financial reports, team progress report, Implementation of Task Force, 1999 September 22 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Downtown Partnership: Meeting notice, agenda, team progress report, minutes, 1988 October 27 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Downtown Partnership: Meeting notice, An overview of the DC Downtown Partnership, wrap-up correspondence, 1989 November 05 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Downtown Partnership: Meeting notice, 1989 strategic plan, 1989/90 proposed budgets, report on Chinatown team, Team reports July 27 1989 -- meeting announcement, agenda, mid-year statement, 1989 strategic plan, Task Force-recommendations, 1989 marketing documents, meeting summary, undated (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Downtown Partnership: Meeting announcement, agenda, mid-year statement, 1989 strategic plan, Task Force -- recommendations, 1989 marketing documents, meeting summary, 1989 July 27 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Downtown Partnership: Meeting notice, agenda, treasurer's report, team presentations, letter to FOX-TV, list of relevant meeting dates, 1989 October 26 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Downtown Partnership: Meeting notice, agenda, 1989 accomplishments, proposed 1990 programs, 1989 financial statement, 1990 proposed budget, meeting summary, 1990 January 24 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Downtown Partnership: Independent Auditor's report and Recommendations, 1990 April 20 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Downtown Partnership: Agenda, 1990 April 27 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Downtown Partnership: Meeting notice, Agenda, 1990 June 05 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Downtown Partnership: Meeting notice, agenda, Chinatown team speaking points, financial status, displaced downtown retailers, meeting summary, 1990 July 26 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Downtown Partnership: Downtown Management District Initiative -- Summary of Findings and Recommendations, 1990 July (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Downtown Partnership: Meeting notice, agenda, holiday marketing and promotions, proposed 1991 budget and programs, 1990 October 25 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Downtown Partnership: Agenda, meeting notice, 1991 April 25 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Downtown Partnership: Summary of Downtown partnership's accomplishments, 1992 December 11 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Downtown Partnership: The Seventh Street Arts Area, 1986 April (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Downtown Partnership: Mayor's Blue Ribbon Committee, 1987 February 02 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Downtown Partnership: Downtown Development Portfolio: Profiles of 1987-1992 projects with Special Emphasis on Retail Space, 1988 April (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Downtown Partnership: Building on Urban Success, Circa 1988 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Downtown Partnership: 1989 Annual Report, undated (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Downtown Partnership: Calendars of Events, 1989 Summer and 1990 Winter issues, undated (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Downtown Partnership: Resource Guide for Small and Minority Retailers, 1990 May (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Downtown Partnership: Downtown Development Portfolio, 1990 October (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Downtown Partnership: Downtown partnership New letters, 1988-1990 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Downtown Partnership: DC Operating and Capital Budgets for 1985 February January, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Downtown Partnership: Mayor's Advisory Committee on Resources and Budget -- Meeting notice and agenda, 1984 March 06 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Downtown Partnership: Mayor's Advisory Committee on Resources and Budget -- meeting minutes, 1984 March 15 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Downtown Partnership: Budgetary Hearing in Chinese Community, 1984 March 17 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Downtown Partnership: Community Budget Conference, February January, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Downtown Partnership: Citizens and the District Budget process, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Downtown Partnership: District of Columbia FY 1985 -- Budget in Brief, undated (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Downtown Partnership: Mayor's Budget Message, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Downtown Partnership: Revenue-Sharing program, undated (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Chinatown Team: History of the Chinese People in Washington, undated (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Chinatown Team: Chinatown notes for brochure, undated (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Chinatown Team: Chinatown Marketing Plan, undated (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Chinatown Team: Summary of Consultants Memorandum Report No. 2 (Market Demand), undated (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Chinatown Team: Chinatown Team Membership, n.d., undated (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Chinatown Team: DC Chinatown Community Survey, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Chinatown Team: Chinatown Program Progress Report 03/1977, undated (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Chinatown Team: Correspondence concerning formation of the Chinatown planning Committee, 1978-1979 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Chinatown Team: Chinatown - Challenges, Possibilities, and Common Myths - paper by AEPA, preliminary draft, 1981 December 19 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Chinatown Team: Outline of the Chinatown program, 1982 December 07 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Chinatown Team: Correspondence -- assistance of Chinatown Team with the metro, 1983 May 05 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Chinatown Team: Updating the Chinatown Program, draft, 1984 May 02 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Chinatown Team: The Chinatown program -- Part of a "Living Downtown", 1984 June (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Chinatown Team: Chinatown program -- detailed membership list, 1984 June 22 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Chinatown Team: Chinatown program -- Economics/Business, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Chinatown Team: Chinatown -- Recent Commercial Development, after 1984, undated (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Chinatown Team: The Chinatown program in 1986, 1986 January (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Chinatown Team: List of new members of the Chinatown Team, 1986 September 24 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Chinatown Team: Chinatown Team -- Meetings and Reports, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Chinatown Team: Correspondence -- request for information on other cities' Chinatowns, 1987 January (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Chinatown Team: DC Office of Planning "The Chinatown Program in 1987" Downtown Washington DC, working draft, 1987 February (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Chinatown Team: Various drafts of the Chinatown Marketing Brochure, 1987 May 29 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Chinatown Team: Estimated Production Cost of the Chinatown Marketing Brochure, 1987 June 24 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Chinatown Team: Draft of the Chinatown "List of Contacts", 1987 June 12 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Chinatown Team: Chinatown Visitor Information Survey -- GWU Internship, 1987 September (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Chinatown Team: Chinatown Visitor Information Survey, prepared for the DC Office of Planning, 1987 December (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Chinatown Team: Chinatown Team -- meetings and reports, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Chinatown Team: Chinatown Team -- meetings and reports, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Chinatown Team: Nominations for members of the Chinatown team, 1988 November 18 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Chinatown Team: The Chinatown Program, various drafts, 1988-1989 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Chinatown Team -- meetings and reports, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Chinatown Team: Reassessment of the Chinatown Team's priorities and programs, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Chinatown Team: Chinatown program promotion -- guidebooks/brochures, 1990 March 09 (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Chinatown Team: Chinatown -- Press Release, 1990 April 26 (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - Chinatown Team: Chinatown program -- looking back: 1990 In Review, discussion draft, 1990 February 04 (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - Chinatown Team: Chinatown program Design Review procedures, article, 1991 February (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - Chinatown Team: Chinatown Program - Looking Back, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - Chinese Community Services, Certificate and Articles of Incorporation, July, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - Documentation of Opium Issue (Yves St. Laurent Perfume) Correspondence, News clippings, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 43)
  - Mayor's Overall Economic Development Advisory Committee, 1980, correspondence, undated (Box 9, Folder 44)
- Wah Luck House, 1977-1982; MS2011 Series 3; 2 Linear feet
  This series consists of materials on the development of the Wah Luck House. The idea for government subsidized housing for Chinatown's residents displaced by the convention center was a concern of the Chinese Consolidated Benevolent Association since the early 1970s. After a long series of grant proposals for development funds and public hearings, the project was finally approved in 1977. This series traces the history of the Wah Luck House from the purchase of the land, through funding, search for an architect, to determining tenant selection. Designed by Alfred Liu in a style termed as "modernism in Chinese dress", it introduced modern Chinese design motifs with red-paneled balconies on the 10 story, 153 unit white apartment building. When Wah Luck house opened in 1982, there were over 1,500 applications. Five years later the waiting list was cut off at 500. It was the last new housing to be built in Chinatown. Material in this series dates from 1977-82.
  - Feasibility Study, April, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Convention Center construction (clippings), 1977-1978 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Convention Center Hearings, testimony, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Background Planning, 1977-1978 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - History and background, misc. correspondence, 1975-1980 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - HUD Urban Development Action Grants, July, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - HUD, Urban Development Action Grants, community letters, regulations, July, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Relocation Assistance Information (HUD), 1979 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Harrison Lee's notebook (memos, letters, re Wah Luck, 1970-1980 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Contractors (letters from companies making bids), n.d., undated (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - National Housing Partnership. Brochures, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - National Center for Housing Management, Inc., Brochures, n.d., undated (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Housing Capital Corporation, brochure, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Donations and Gifts, n.d., undated (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Harrison Lee's notes on conference calls, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - General background correspondence (H. Lee's original folder), 1977-1979 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Public Hearings, Press Release, 1978 January (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - HUD Block Grant Guidelines, Draft, 1978 January (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Loan Application, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Proposed Chinese Community Center, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence - National Corporation of Housing Project, 1980-1983 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Architects/Proposals -- Alfred Liu, undated (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Architects/Proposals -- Donohoe, undated (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Architects/Proposals -- Ronald Hsu, undated (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Architects/Proposals -- James G. Davis, undated (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Architects/Proposals -- Klein, Clarens, Tong and Widome, undated (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Architects/Proposals -- P.E.C. Park and Company (1), undated (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Architects/Proposals -- P.E.C. Park and Company (2), undated (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Architects/Proposals -- Saunders, Cheng, and Appleton, undated (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Architects/Proposals -- Wanchul Lee Associates PC, undated (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Social Services, Proposed programs, staff, undated (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Community Activity Facility, undated (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - HUD Application, Section 202/8 Forms, correspondence, undated (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - HUD, Correspondence re grant, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Limited Partnership (Chinatown Dev. Corp and National Corp. for Housing Partnership, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - IRS, Tax Exemption, undated (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Development Fees Agreement, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Development Fees Agreement, 1980-1981 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Washington Chinatown Development Company Certification, undated (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Financing, correspondence, resources, undated (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Housing for the Elderly, examples of brochures, floor plans of existing projects, n.d., undated (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Grand Opening, press releases, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Initial Closing Documents, Part I, 1981 March 31 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Initial Closing Documents, Part II. 03/31/1981, undated (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Application for Section 220 Mortgage Insurance, undated (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - National Corp. for Housing Partnerships, correspondence re closing and settlement, undated (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Sales Contract, Lot 52, Square 453, March 31, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Manager position, applications, evaluation, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Ground Breaking Ceremony, 1981 May 09 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Original Purchase Agreements (investors and Nat. Corp. for Housing Partnership, June, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Certificate of Achievement, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Opening articles, press releases, letters, undated (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Invitation List for Dedication of Wah Luck, 1982 September 19 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Ad for apartments, Shoppers Guide, 1982 October 15 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Proposed Social Services Program, 1982 November (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - HUD, Economic Dev. Conference, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Final Closing Documents, 1983 April 14 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Final Closing Documents, 1983 April 14 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Meditation Garden, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Financial Statement, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - HUD, memo re Section 202, re conflict of interest policy, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Tenants -- Lists of names, actions, comments, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Contact report, 1982 July 30 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Application forms, leases, undated (Box 13, Folder 19)